Felipe Dolago

Cedar Park, TX 78613 | +01 (254) 681-7065 | lagofelipe@gmail.com

PROFILE

Adaptable and dedicated professional with over a decade of Account Management, Customer Interaction and Data Analysis experience leading and managing cross-functional teams and delivering customer-centric marketing strategies and solutions to increase productivity and drive business revenue. Outstanding communication, analytical, problem-solving, leadership, interpersonal and teamwork abilities. Fluent in English, Spanish and Portuguese.

SKILLS

Business Analyst | Project Management | Business Development | Customer Success | Client Relations | Strategic Account Management | Customer Retention | B2B | Leadership | CRM | Consulting | MS Office | Analytics | Tableau | SQL | RAILS | Data | SalesForce | SAP | GSA Ready | Top Secret Clearance | Process Improvement | Reliable

EXPERIENCE

Accenture Austin, TX, USA

Google & YouTube, product under GSO- Platform Associate/Quality Analyst

August 2021 - Present

- Achieved high quality performance as a content moderation admin and SME, and in-depth understanding of specific workflow policies.
- Effectively conducted root cause analysis for workflow, creating action plans to stakeholders.

Hays City Corp.

Austin, TX, USA

Tex-con Oil & Motiva Enterprises Partnership - Operations-Team Lead

November 2014 – July 2020

- Boosted baseline workload and efficiency by moving all planning and ordering into SmartLogix. Lead time changed from 24 to 48 hrs, a 100% improvement on lead and delivery times.
- Helped to achieve team member retention in a very competitive tech and sales market, introducing cross-training
 to increase team redundancy to eliminate the risk of single experts, and reversed a previously high turnover
 department.

Suncoast Resources Inc. Houston, TX, USA

Suncoast Resources Austin, Operations – Warehouse Manager

July 2012-November 2014

- Lead a team in verifying and inspecting shipments in order to ensure delivery of optimal quality merchandise while improving safety scores and lead times.
- Managed location inventory, prepared and completed monthly inventory reporting.

U.S. Army Gunsan, South Korea

AMEED MEDPROS certified Trainer / Analyst

March 2010 -July 2012

- Healthcare Specialist(68W) with Top Secret Clearance assigned to USAF 8th Wing. (Kunsan AFB, South Korea)
- Primarily oversaw and trained officer personnel on MEDPROS (USMEDACC) CRM software and its initial implementation in the Asian theater.

EDUCATION_

Flatiron School Austin, TX, USA

Software Engineering immersive Bootcamp

United States Army Medical Center and School

November 2010

August 2020

AMEED Health Care Specialist

Universidade Gama Filho

Rio De Janeiro, RJ, Brazil

San Antonio, TX, USA

Bachelor of Business Administration

July 2008